Guide to the Ailecia Ruscin Zine Collection, 1994-2002 and undated RL.01120
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Ailecia Ruscin Zine collection
1994-2002 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Ruscin, Ailecia (collector)
RL.01120
7.2 Linear Feet
The collection consists of 552 zines, collected by the donor between 1994 and 2001. The collection focuses on personal zines by women, politics, the punk music scene, social justice activism, and riot grrrl. Many of the zines are accompanied by correspondence with the donor. Ailecia Ruscin is a writer, activist, and scholar from San Antonio, Texas and Auburn, Alabama. She is the author or co-author of the zines provo-CAT-ive and alabama grrrl (published from 1997-2000).
552 Items
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Provenance
The Ailecia Ruscin Zine Collection was received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift in 2005.
Biographical Note
Ailecia Ruscin, of San Antonio, Texas and Auburn, Alabama, is a writer, activist, and scholar. She received a Bachelor of Arts in Cultural Studies and Environmental Studies from Chatham College in 1999 and, as of 2008, is completing a Ph.D. in American Studies at the University of Kansas. Ruscin is the author or co-author of the zines provo-CAT-ive and alabama grrrl (published from 1997-2000); an excerpt from provo-CAT-ive was included in A Girl's Guide to Taking Over the World: Writings From The Girl Zine Revolution, edited by Tristan Taormino and Karen Green, and excerpts from alabama grrrl have been included in The Zine Yearbook. Ruscin is one of the founding members of Solidarity! Revolutionary Center and Radical Library, an anarchist infoshop in Lawrence, Kansas; has served on the advisory boards of Allied Media Projects and Clamor magazine; and contributes zine reviews to Zine World.
Collection Overview
The collection consists of 552 zines, collected by the donor between 1994 and 2001. The collection focuses on personal zines by women, politics, the punk music scene, social justice activism, and riot grrrl. Many of the zines are accompanied by correspondence with the donor. Acquired as part of the Sallie Bingham Center for Women's History and Culture.
Self-publishing; Political activists -- Southern States; Women -- Comic books, strips, etc.; Underground press publications -- United States; Young women -- United States -- Social life and customs; Fan magazines; Comic books, strips, etc.; Feminism -- United States; Periodicals -- Publishing -- United States; Ruscin, Ailecia (collector); Sallie Bingham Center for Women's History and Culture
- Aberration, no.12, August 1998 (Box 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Milwaukee, WI
- Activist Approach to Domestic Violence (Box 1)
  Seattle, WA
- Adele, no.5, 1999 (Box 1)
  San Francisco, CA
- Adorn, no.10 (Box 1)
  Hartville, OH
- Air I Breathe, no.2, Fall 1998 (Box 1)
  Northampton, MA
- AK Press Catalog, 2001 (Box 1)
- Alabama Grrrl, no.8 (Box 1)
  Lawrence, KS
- Alaska (Box 1)
  Irvine, CA
- Alien, no.10, April 1997 (Box 1)
  Pacific Palisades, CA
- Alien, no.11 (Box 1)
- Alley Brat, no.1 (Box 1)
  Fullerton, CA
- Alternatives to Pads and Tampons (Box 1)
- Alternatives to Tampons (Box 1)
  Philadelphia, PA
- Amusing Yourself to Death: A Guide to Surfing the Papernet (Box 1)
  Santa Barbara, CA
- Amusing Yourself to Death: A Guide to Surfing the Papernet, no.11, April/May 1998 (Box 1)
- Anarchism: The Feminist Connection (Box 1)
- Annzine, no.4, Spring 1996 (Box 1)
- Anorexic Mishaps (and other reasons to revolt) (Box 1)
- Anorexic Mishaps (and other reasons to revolt), no.4 (Box 1)
- Anti-Punk, no.7 (Box 1)
  Denver, CO
- Aptitude & Appetite, no.1, January 1998 (Box 1)
  Pittsburgh, PA
- Aptitude & Appetite, no.2, February 1998 (Box 1)
- Aqua Girl Star, no.2 (Box 1)
  Marysville, CA
- Arrowed, no.3, Fall 1998 (Box 1)
  New York, NY
- Arrowed, no.6 (Box 1)
- Arrowed, no.8 (Box 1)
- Art Machine: Former title: Rising, no.2, January 2000 (Box 1)
  South Bend, IN
- Assassin and the Whiner: "cool comics by Carrie and Sarah", no.12, 2000 (Box 1)
  Los Angeles, CA
- Assassin and the Whiner: "cool comics by Carrie and Sarah", no.7, 1997 (Box 1)
- Automatic Pansy, no.18, September 1999 (Box 1)
  Baltimore, MD
- Automatic Pansy, no.20, June 2000 (Box 1)
- AWOL: Youth for Peace and Revolution, no.3 (Box 1)
- B.B.'s Revenge, no.3 (Box 1)
  Richmond Hill, NY
- B.B.'s Revenge, no.4 (Box 1)
- Baby Girl, no.3 (Box 1)
  Jacksonville, FL
- Baby Girl, no.5, April 1999 (Box 1)
- Backlash, November 1998 (Box 1)
- Bacon, no.1, 1998 (Box 1)
- Bamboo Girl, no.10, January 2001 (Box 1)
- Bamboo Girl, no.6 (Box 1)
- Bamboo Girl, no.8, January 1999 (Box 1)
- Bamboo Girl, no.9, 2000 (Box 1)
- BananaQ, no.3 (Box 1)
- Bandit Queen Distribution (Box 1)
- Banshee, no.3, Summer 1999 (Box 1)
  Prairie Village, KS
- Be Nice or I'll Fucking Kill You, no.1 (Box 2)
  Brooklyn, NY
- Being Red: A novelette by Heather Lynn, November 1999 (Box 2)
  Grayslake, IL
- Belly Up, no.3 (Box 2)
  Portland, OR
- Belly Up, no.4 (Box 2)
- Bernadette the Squirrel, no.5 (Box 2)
  Wilkinsburg, PA
- Beyond a Joke, no.1 (Box 2)
  Fairfax, VA
- Beyond, no.1, Autumn 1999 (Box 2)
  Hannover, Germany
- Beyond, no.2, May 2000 (Box 2)
- Billy's Mitten, no.3, 1995 (Box 2)
  Tucson, AZ
- Bitch Nation, no.7 (Box 2)
- Bitchcore, no.1, September 1999 (Box 2)
  Pasadena, CA
- Blender Children, no.1, 1998 (Box 2)
  Topeka, KS
- Blender Children, no.2, October 1999 (Box 2)
- Blender Children, no.3, December 1999 (Box 2)
- Blue Skies, no.2, November 2000 (Box 2)
  Portland, ME
- Book Your Own Fuckin' Life: A do-it-yourself resource guide, no.7, 1999 (Box 2)
- Book Your Own Fuckin' Life: A do-it-yourself resource guide, no.9, 2001 (Box 2)
- Book, no.5 (Box 2)
- Book, no.7.5 (Box 2)
- Boredom Sucks, March-April 1995 (Box 2)
  Staten Island, NY
- Bottled Up, no.2 (Box 2)
- Boy & Girl, September 2000 (Box 2)
  Brampton, Ontario, Canada
- Brat: "because your school paper sucks," no.8, 1998 (Box 2)
  Louisiville, KY
- Brazen Hussy Comics (Box 2)
  Gainesville, FL
- Breakdown, no.4 (Box 2)
  Sacramento, CA
- Brewster, no.1 (Box 2)
  Wheat Ridge, CO
- Brewster, no.1.5 (Box 2)
- Brewster, no.2, February 2000 (Box 2)
- Broken Distro, October 2000 (Box 2)
  Scituate, MA
- Broken Pencil: Zine culture in Canada and around the world, no.13, Summer 2000 (Box 2)
  Toronto, Ontario, Canada
- Bruja, no.1, 1998 (Box 2)
- Burnt, no.2 (Box 2)
  Parsippany, NJ
- Business as Usual, no.1 (Box 2)
  Greensburg, PA
- C. Parks, no.1 (Box 2)
- C. Parks, no.3, 1996 (Box 2)
- Cacofonia Deliciosa, no.3 (Box 2)
  Watertown, MA
- Cacofonia Deliciosa, no.4 (Box 2)
- Cain, no.2, 1999 (Box 2)
  New Haven, CT
- Cakewalk (Box 2)
  Ambridge, PA
- Candy Coated Teeth, January 1999 (Box 2)
  Ithaca, NY and Pownal, ME
- Cataclysm Girl, no.6 (Box 2)
  Chicopee, MA
- Cemented Youth: Formerly Lion Un-Taming, no.3, 1999 (Box 2)
  Los Osos, CA
- Chard Copy: Rainbow Grocery Cooperative Newsletter, vol. 2, no. 1 (Box 2)
- Chard Copy: Rainbow Grocery Cooperative Newsletter, vol. 2, no. 2 (Box 2)
- Cheap Porn and Bad Food, 1999 (Box 2)
- Cherry Cherry Red, no.5, 1999 (Box 2)
- Chickfactor, no.12, 1999 (Box 2)
  New York, NY and Washington, DC
- Chokehold, 1999 (Box 2)
- Christine Bactine, no.1, Fall 1999 (Box 3)
  St. Albans, WV
- Cloudland, 1998 (Box 3)
  Cumming, GA
- Con Queso, no.1, November 1999 (Box 3)
- Confluence, no. 5 (Box 3)
  St. Louis, MO
- Consider Yourself Kissed, no.2, Summer 1999 (Box 3)
  Lenexa, KS
- Consider Yourself Kissed, no.3, February 2000 (Box 3)
- Consider Yourself Kissed, no.4 (Box 3)
- Cory, 1999 (Box 3)
  Malta, NY
- Counterclockwise: Angels of the Fall, no.2 (Box 3)
- Cracker, no.3, 1999 (Box 3)
  Vicksburg, MS
- Cracker, no.5 (Box 3)
- Crazed Sparrow, no.2 (Box 3)
- Crazed Sparrow, no.3 (Box 3)
- Creamsicle (Box 3)
  Gettysburg, PA
- Creamsicle (Box 3)
- Crescent, Spring 1999 (Box 3)
  Auburn, AL
- Crude Noise (Box 3)
  New Orleans, LA
- Crush Zine (Box 3)
  Havre de Grace, MD
- Cuntfear, no.1 (Box 3)
- Cupsize, no.3, Winter 1995 (Box 3)
- Cupsize, no.4 (Box 3)
- Cupsize, vol. 1, no. 2 (Box 3)
- curmudgeon, 1993 (Box 3)
  Mission Viejo, CA
- Cuss, no.2, 1996 (Box 3)
  New Wilmington, PA
- Cyanide, no.2, March 1999 (Box 3)
  Santa Monica, CA
- dead glamorous, 1998-1999 (Box 3)
  Vernon Hills, IL
- Death of a Psyche, no.5 (Box 3)
  Scottsdale, AZ
- Death of a Psyche, no.6 (Box 3)
- Death Ship, no.2, Late 2002 (Box 3)
  Hayward, CA
- Deconstruction, no.1, September 1998 (Box 3)
- Defenestrator: Philly's newspaper for anarchy and action, no.16, May 2001 (Box 3)
- Delivery Dyke, no.1 (Box 3)
- Della Dart & Rachel Jacobs (Box 3)
- Demigod (Box 3)
  Doylestown, PA
- Demigod (Box 3)
- Disgruntl T.V., no.14, October-November 1994 (Box 3)
  Richton Park, IL
- Disgruntl T.V., no.16, December 1994-January1995 (Box 3)
- Disgruntl T.V., no.17 (Box 3)
- Disgruntl T.V., no.18, November 1995-January 1996 (Box 3)
- Disorderly Conduct, no.2, Winter 2000-2001 (Box 3)
- Disorientation Guide, 2002 (Box 3)
- Divinity, 1999 January (Box 3)
  Evansville, IN
- Dixie Cup, no.1 (Box 3)
  Austin, TX
- DIY Crafts Primer (Box 3)
  Bowling Green, OH
- DMZ: The Magazine of YouthPeace, no.5 (Box 3)
- Dodo, no.2, 1998 (Box 3)
  Washington DC,
- Dogfish, no.7 (Box 3)
  Manchester, MO
- Donald's Date, Winter 2002 (Box 3)
- Don't Stop (Stop), no.1 (Box 3)
  Amherst, MA
- Doris, no.11 (Box 4)
  Asheville, NC
- Doris, no.12 (Box 4)
- Doris, no.13 (Box 4)
- Doris, no.16, Summer 2000 (Box 4)
- Doris, no.17 (Box 4)
- Doris, no.18 (Box 4)
- Doris, no.6 (Box 4)
- Doris, no.9 (Box 4)
- Double Negative, no.16 (Box 4)
- Douze Jours En France: 12 Days in France, 1999 (Box 4)
- Dream whip, no.8 (Box 4)
  Lubbock, TX
- Dream whip, no.9 (Box 4)
- Drivel, no.3 (Box 4)
  Overland Park, KS
- Drivel, no.6, December 2000 (Box 4)
- Ducks in a Row, no.1 (Box 4)
  Cupertino, CA
- Dumb Fun, no.12 (Box 4)
  Regina, SK, Canada
- Dumpsterland, no.8 (Box 4)
  Chicago, IL
- East Village Inky, no.10 (Box 4)
- Electrocution Distribution, late 2000 (Box 4)
  Queensland, Australia
- Emergency, no.3 (Box 4)
- Epi-Logue (Box 4)
- Epson Energy, no.1, April 1999 (Box 4)
  Washington, DC,
- Equilibrium, no.3, Summer 1999 (Box 4)
  Albany/Brooklyn, NY
- Estrogen Overdose/Dysfunxion, no.1 (Box 4)
  Makati City, Philippines
- Evolution of a Race Riot, August 1997 (Box 4)
  Berkeley, CA
- Exploding Girl, no.1 (Box 4)
  Severna Park, MD
- Factura No Pagada, no.5 (Box 4)
  Guayama, Puerto Rico
- Fairy Flower Distro, no.1, July 1998 (Box 4)
  New Orleans, LA: Fairy Flower
- Fancy, no.10 (Box 4)
  Boston, MA
- Fancy, no.11, Midwinter 1998-99 (Box 4)
- Fancy, no.12, June-July 1999 (Box 4)
- Fancy, no.8, March/April 1998 (Box 4)
- Fancy, no.9 (Box 4)
- Fantastic Fanzine, no.6 (Box 4)
  Arlington, VA
- Fantasy Cat, no.3 (Box 4)
- Feminist as Fuck, no.1 (Box 4)
  Tampa, FL
- Femme Flicke, no.6 (Box 4)
  Cambridge, MA
- Femmestruation Rites Rag, March 2000 (Box 4)
- Fern, no.11 (Box 4)
- Fiano Apple is Feeding the Tree (Box 4)
  Byhalie, MS
- Floating Bear Zine, no.4 (Box 4)
  Kalamazoo, MI
- Flowers from the Rain, no.1 (Box 4)
  Arcata, CA
- Fly Pink Hair, no.2 (Box 4)
  Washington Depot, CT
- Flying Lesson, no.4, 2000 (Box 4)
  Bloomington, IN
- Food Geek, no.3 (Box 4)
- For Anne (Box 4)
  Carson City, NV
- Forget the Show, no.2, July 1999 (Box 4)
  Virginia Beach, VA
- Fragile, 2000 January (Box 4)
  Minneapolis, MN
- Fuck Off Western Medicine: A woman's right: booklet for DIY cunt care (Box 4)
  Columbus, OH
- Function, no.11 (Box 4)
- Futotcho, no.4, 1999 (Box 4)
- Future Generation, no.9 (Box 4)
  Fairfield, PA
- Girl and her Bike, no.7, July 2000 (Box 5)
  Winnipeg, Manitoba, Canada
- Girl Face Girl (Box 5)
- Girl in a Box, no.4, 1999 July (Box 5)
  Port Chester, NY
- Girl in a Box, no.5, 2000 February (Box 5)
  New York City, NY
- Girl Patch: The Transition Issue, no.6, 1997 Autumn (Box 5)
- Girl Swirl Fanzine, no.3 (Box 5)
- Girl Swirl Fanzine, no.4 (Box 5)
- Girl's Life Magazine, vol. 1, issue 1, 1996-1997 Winter (Box 5)
- Glitter Queer, 1996 (Box 5)
- Goddess (Box 5)
  Hillsborough, NC
- Goddess Juice (Box 5)
- God's Own Methane, March 2000 (Box 5)
  Kansas City, MO
- Good Mornin (Box 5)
- Good Not Bad (Box 5)
  New Lebanon, NY
- Good Swift Kick, no.2 (Box 5)
- Gray Matters Magzine, 1998 Spring (Box 5)
- Gray Matters Magzine, 1998 Summer (Box 5)
- Gray Matters Magzine, 1999 Winter (Box 5)
- Gray Matters Magzine, 1999 Summer (Box 5)
- Grrlz on the Road, September 1998 (Box 5)
  London, England
- Grub: Fine good for Dumb Shits, no.10 (Box 5)
  Iowa City, Iowa, IA
- Gumption, no.3 (Box 5)
  Ann Arbor, MI
- Guts, no.6 (Box 5)
  Lynn, MA
- Gutsy, no.2 (Box 5)
  Rowland Heights, CA
- Harbinger, undated (Box 5)
  Atlanta, GA
- Harbinger (Box 5)
- Heart Attack, no.1 (Box 5)
- Heartattack, no.26, 2000 May (Box 5)
  Goleta, CA
- Heartattack: Hard Core, no.22, May 1999 (Box 5)
- Heartfelt, no.3 (Box 5)
- Held Like Sound, no.5, 1999 Spring/Summer (Box 5)
  Kensington, MD
- Hello Nothing, no.14, June 2000 (Box 5)
  Winter Springs, FL
- Here Be Dragons, no.1, ca. 1997 (Box 5)
- Here Be Dragons, no.3, ca. 1998 (Box 5)
- Here Be Dragons, no.4 (Box 5)
- Here Be Dragons, no.6, 1999 August (Box 5)
- Hodgepodge, no.5, January 1999 (Box 5)
  Buffalo, NY
- Hollywood Nihil, no.1 (Box 5)
- Honey Child, ca. 1998 (Box 5)
  Orlando, FL
- Hot Pantz (Box 5)
  Montreal, Quebec, Canada
- House of Anarchy, no.2, ca. 1999 (Box 5)
- House of Anarchy, no.4 (Box 5)
- How I Learned to Do IT Bloody Murder, 1998 (Box 5)
- How to Stage a Coup: An Insurrection of the Underground Liberation Army, undated (Box 5)
  Scarborough, Ontario, Canada
- I Am Not a Sell-Out (Box 5)
  Beverly Hills, CA
- I am not pretty: and this is not your cup of tea, December 1998 (Box 5)
  Laguna Niguel, CA
- I Blot Under the Milk, no.124, 1994 Winter (Box 5)
  Berea, OH
- I Crossed My Heart Catalog, no.2, 1999 Fall (Box 5)
  Morris, IL
- I Draw Starz, 1999 (Box 5)
  Arroyo Grande, CA
- I Dreamed I Was Assertive!, no.2, Winter 1999 (Box 5)
- I Dreamed I Was Assertive!, no.3, Winter/Spring 2000 (Box 5)
- I Think I Am, no.1, ca. 2000 (Box 5)
- I Was a Teenage Girl Army (Box 6)
  Little Rock, AR
- I Will Not Be Afraid: the true revolution, no.1, March 2000 (Box 6)
  Everett, WA
- Idiolect, no.1, 1999 August (Box 6)
  Newport Center, VT
- Imps in the Inkwell: Bitch, no.2, 1997 September (Box 6)
  Minneapolis, MN: Hellespont Publications
- Imps in the Inkwell: Body, no.3, 1997 December (Box 6)
- Imps in the Inkwell: Idol, no.7, 1999 Spring (Box 6)
- Imps in the Inkwell: Monster, no.4, 1998 March (Box 6)
- Imps in the Inkwell: Pain, no.6, 1998 September (Box 6)
- Imps in the Inkwell: Vice, no.5, 1998 June (Box 6)
- In Abandon, no.4, Spring 1999 (Box 6)
- in memory of a carsurfer: a kiss on the cheek of misplaced people and rawkers with a uterus, 2000 (Box 6)
  Milwaukee, WI,
- In Morning Clouds / Treefort, no.13 / 12, 1999 August (Box 6)
  Ottawa, Ontario, Canada
- In Morning Clouds, no.14, 2000 January (Box 6)
  Wolfville, Nova Scotia, Canada
- In Morning Clouds, no.15, 2000 July (Box 6)
- In Morning Clouds, no.9 (Box 6)
- Independent Publishing Resource Center Brochure, undated (Box 6)
- Indulgence, no.1, August 1998 (Box 6)
  Pownal, ME
- Indulgence, no.2, January 1999 (Box 6)
- Indulgence, no.3, May 1999 (Box 6)
- Indulgence, no.4, 1999 October (Box 6)
- Indulgence, no.5, 2000 Summer (Box 6)
- Indulgence, no.6 (Box 6)
- Insisterhood, no.1 (Box 6)
  Sechelt, British Columbia, Canada
- Insisterhood, no.2 (Box 6)
- Invincible Summer, March 2001 (Box 6)
- Jailhouse Turnout: JTO (Box 6)
  Greencastle, IN
- Jigsaw, no.5.5, ca. 1994 (Box 6)
  Olympia, WA
- Journal of an Insomniac (Box 6)
- Journalsong, no.3, December 2000 (Box 6)
- Justseeds, 2001 (Box 6)
- Keep Yer Kitty Wet: The Choice Issue, no.2, ca. 1997 October (Box 6)
  Hanford, CA
- Ker-bloom!, Mar.-Apr. 1997 (Box 6)
  Oakland, CA: artnoose
- Ker-bloom!, no.5, March/April 1997 (Box 6)
  Oakland, CA
- Kiss Off, no.6, undated (Box 6)
- Kusp, no.1, 1995 Summer (Box 6)
  Gaithersburg, MD
- Kusp, no.3, 1996 Summer (Box 6)
- La Ciudad, 1999 (Box 6)
  Culver City, CA: The Angry Red Planet
- Lady Lazarus, no.2, undated (Box 6)
- Last Chance, 1999 (Box 6)
  Bennington, VT
- Law of Inertia, no.7, Winter/Spring 2000 (Box 6)
  Ithaca, NY
- Leeking Ink, no.23, 2000 December (Box 7)
- Leeking Ink: The Minutia Issue, no.24, 2001 July (Box 7)
- Lefty Makes a Better Cake (Box 7)
  Midland Park, NJ
- Lemon Meringue, no.7, undated (Box 7)
- Lesbian Connection, vol. 24, no. 1 (Box 7)
  East Lansing, MI
- Libel Alien Idiot Nation (Box 7)
- Limousine / That Girl, no.5 / 9, 1997 August (Box 7)
  San Luis Obispo / San Francisco, CA
- Lip Synch, undated (Box 7)
- LIPP Service: Loud Intelligent Political People, no.1, Winter 2000 (Box 7)
- Lipstick My Espionage, no.3 (Box 7)
  Rockford, IL
- Liquid Thoughtz (Box 7)
- Little Super Human Guy, no.12 (Box 7)
  Potsdam, NY
- Little Super Human Guy, no.6, 1998 April/May (Box 7)
  Liverpool, NY
- Losing My Religion: The Fear of Falling Issue, no.4, 2000 Fall (Box 7)
- Love Letter, no.3, ca. 2001 February (Box 7)
- Love Letter: An Existence of Haves & Have-Nots, no.1, ca. 2000 January (Box 7)
- Love Letter: Do You Know Rainbow?, no.1/2, undated (Box 7)
- Lovezine, no.1, undated (Box 7)
  Richmond, VA
- Lucky Lucky (Box 7)
  Gahanna, OH
- Lust and Lunacy, 1999 May (Box 7)
  San Jose, CA
- Make Out (Box 7)
  Vancouver, British Columbia, Canada
- Mantis, no.2, undated (Box 7)
  Willoughby, OH
- Mantis, no.3 (Box 7)
- Matilda, no.6, Winter 2001 (Box 7)
- Matilda, no.7, 2001 Spring (Box 7)
- Maximumquillnscrol: Texttrap Catalog, Winter 2000 (Box 7)
- Maximumrocknroll, no.198, November 1999 (Box 7)
- Maximumrocknroll, no.202, March 2000 (Box 7)
- Maximumrocknroll, no.3, January 2000 (Box 7)
- Me. (Box 7)
- Melt the Snow, no.7, March 1998 (Box 7)
  Weston, Ontario
- Memorytown USA, no.1, Summer 1998 (Box 7)
  Middletown, CT
- Message to the Black Movement: A Political Statement from the Black Underground (Box 7)
- Millenniumitis: look hope move, no.2, August 1999 (Box 7)
- Miranda, no.4, 1999 March (Box 7)
- Miranda, no.5, 1999 December (Box 7)
- MOC (Box 7)
- Mommy and I Are One, no.7, Summer/Fall 1999 (Box 7)
  Allston, MA
- monkey's magical book of cheese: (and strawberries too!) (Box 7)
  Bedford Park, IL
- Monsters are Real, no.2 (Box 7)
  Northport, FL
- More Signs You do Zine, June 1999 (Box 7)
- Move Closer, 1999 Summer (Box 7)
  Washington, DC
- Moving Parts, no.1 (Box 7)
- Muffin Bones: The Travel and Holiday Issue, no.19, 1998 Spring (Box 7)
- Multiple Sarcasm, no.1, 2000 (Box 7)
  Carmel, IN: Jekylbunny Publications
- Multiple Sarcasm, no.2, 2000 (Box 7)
- My Best Friend, ca. 1998 (Box 8)
- My Green Bag, no.1, undated (Box 8)
  Toledo, OH
- My Own Personal Star (Box 8)
- My Views Change Over Time, no.3, 1998 December (Box 8)
- Nerdy Grrrl Revolution, no.2, undated (Box 8)
- New Faggot Cunts (Box 8)
- Nice Girls Don't Say Fuck You, undated (Box 8)
  Oro Station, Ontario, Canada
- Night of Vice, 1998 (Box 8)
  Minneapolis, MN: Hellespont Comix
- Nipples and Bits: Back in Mississippi, no.1, undated (Box 8)
- No More Tears Left to Cry, no.2, undated (Box 8)
- Not My Small Diary, no.3, ca. 1997 (Box 8)
  Birmingham, AL
- Not My Small Diary, no.4, undated (Box 8)
- Now a Limo (Box 8)
- Now a Limo, no.2 (Box 8)
- Now a Limo, no.3 (Box 8)
- Now a Limo, no.4 (Box 8)
- Octopus Head Collective, no.2, ca. 1999 (Box 8)
- Octopus Head Collective, no.3, ca. 2000 (Box 8)
- Off My Jammy: La Cuarta, no.4, undated (Box 8)
  Albany, NY
- Okefenokee (Box 8)
  , GA
- Opening Statement, April 2000 (Box 8)
  Bartlesville, OK
- Operation Kitty Kitty, no.3, 2000 Spring (Box 8)
  Uncasville, CT
- Operation Kitty Kitty: O.K.K., no.4, 2001 Winter (Box 8)
- Opposites Subtract, no.2, undated (Box 8)
  Alamo, CA
- Oppress This Zine, no.10, undated (Box 8)
  Avon Lake, OH
- Oppress This, no.11, Winter 1999/Spring 2000 (Box 8)
- Oppress This, no.8 (Box 8)
- Other Ramona, no.1 (Box 8)
  Kingston, Ontario, Canada
- Out of Order, no.2, 1999 May-June (Box 8)
  Cedar Falls, IA
- Out of the Vortex, no.6, 1994 Autumn (Box 8)
- Outburst: A Delicious Zine, no.8, undated (Box 8)
  Chesapeake, VA
- Outdated La-oo-ra: My Kiwiland Adventure: A Year in the Life of a Girl Overseas, no.1, undated (Box 8)
- Pain on Earth: An X-mas Diary, 1997 (Box 8)
- Pander Zine Distro, 1999 Fall-Winter (Box 8)
- Pander Zine Distro, 2000-2001 Winter (Box 8)
- Pander Zine Distro: a mailorder catalog, Spring/Summer 2001 (Box 8)
- Pansy, no.1 (Box 8)
  Edmonds, WA
- Paperdoll, no.3 (Box 8)
  Galesburg, MI
- Paranoy, no.14, undated (Box 8)
  St. Peter, MN
- Paroxysm (Box 8)
  Washington D.C.
- Passionate Frog, no.2, 1998 September (Box 8)
  Brockton, MA
- Peach, no.4 (Box 8)
- Peculiar Twirling Skirt, 1999 (Box 8)
- Pedestrian Parallax, no.1, 2001 Summer (Box 8)
  Durham, NC
- Penguins & Alligators: A Collection of Cartoons and Ruminations, no.3, 1998 August (Box 8)
- Period Conspiracy (Box 8)
- Persnickety Prints, undated (Box 8)
  Blackwood, NJ
- Picaflor, no.1, September 1999 (Box 8)
- Pink Tea, no.4 (Box 8)
- Pippi Longstocking, undated (Box 8)
  Easton, MA
- Pisces Ladybug, no.3, 1995-1996 Winter (Box 8)
  West Bethesda, MD
- Pisces Zine Distro and Fun Stuff Catalog, no.10, 1999 Summer (Box 8)
- Pisces Zine Distro and Fun Stuff Catalog, no.9, 1999 Spring (Box 8)
- Pixxiebitch, no.3, undated (Box 8)
  Montrose, PA
- Planet Named Desire, no.1, 1996-1997 (Box 8)
  Tucson, AZ: Pullet Pub.
- Plunger, no.3, 1994 December (Box 8)
- PMS, no.9 (Box 8)
- Polarity / Freewheeler, no.16 / 11, 1997 December (Box 8)
  Jamestown / Tucson, CA / AZ
- Polaroid Manifesto, undated (Box 9)
- Political Art: A resource zine by Ailecia Ruscin, the Alabama Grrrl (Box 9)
- Poor Children, no.5 (Box 9)
- Pout, no.4, undated (Box 9)
  North Kingstown, RI
- Pout, no.5, undated (Box 9)
- Pout, no.6, undated (Box 9)
- Power Candy, no.16, 1996 April (Box 9)
- Primordial Soup Kitchen, no.1, July-September 1998 (Box 9)
  Claremont, CA
- Pritty Kitty Clothes (Box 9)
  North Royalton, OH
- Project Pinky, no.1, undated (Box 9)
  Santa Fe Springs, CA
- Projet Mobilivre-Bookmobile Project Brochure, 2001 (Box 9)
- Pull the Plug…on the feminine hygiene industry (Box 9)
  Jamaica Plain, MA
- Pulled Mints, Spring 1995 (Box 9)
  Richmond, VA: Voit & Levinson
- Pulled Mints, no.1, Fall 1994 (Box 9)
- Puncture, no.47, Fall 2000 (Box 9)
- Punkindex: A zine devoted to punk (whatever that is) (Box 9)
- Queen of the Kangaroos, 2000 (Box 9)
  Blue Island, IL
- Queer Resource Mini-Zine, October 1999 (Box 9)
- Queer Zine Explosion, no.17, 1999 August (Box 9)
- Queer Zine Explosion, no.19, 2001 June/July (Box 9)
- Rad Girlz (Box 9)
- Rage Against, no.2, undated (Box 9)
  Worcester, MA
- Rainbow Pudding, no.1, undated (Box 9)
  Gilroy, CA
- Rampage: or The Diaries of Two Sex Crazed Riot Chyx, 1995 October (Box 9)
  Knoxville, TN
- RATE: Rough Around the Edges, no.3, April 2000 (Box 9)
- Rather Be Dead Than Cool, vol. 71, no. 10, undated (Box 9)
  Hartford, CT: UnCooL Productions
- Raw Sugar, 1999 August-December (Box 9)
- Razorcake, no.1, March/April 2001 (Box 9)
- Record Reviews (Box 9)
- Red Scare, no.1, 2000 Summer-Fall (Box 9)
  Chapel Hill, NC
- Red Scare, no.2 (Box 9)
- Red Under, no.6, September 2000 (Box 9)
  Memphis, TN
- Red-Hooded Sweatshirt, no.1, 1998 (Box 9)
- Red-Hooded Sweatshirt, no.3, 1999 Fall-Winter (Box 9)
- Renegade's Handbook to Love and Sabotage, no.1, April 2000 (Box 9)
- Renegade's Handbook to Love and Sabotage, no.3, 2001 March (Box 9)
- Retail Whore, no.3, undated (Box 10)
- Retail Whore, no.4, undated (Box 10)
- Retail Whore, no.5, November 2001 (Box 10)
- Riot Dyke, undated (Box 10)
  Tulsa, OK
- Riot Grrrl, undated (Box 10)
- Riot Grrrl Montreal (Box 10)
- Riot Grrrl Press: RGP, no.2, 1999 July-December (Box 10)
- Rocket Queen (Box 10)
- Rocksta, undated (Box 10)